HEY!
HEY. WOW, IT IS
TRUE WHAT THEY SAY:
PREGNANT BELLIES
LOOK LIKE A DRUM.
HA, HA.
NO, IT'S JUST,
I'M SO PREGNANT
THAT MY GUITAR
DOESN'T FIT ANYMORE
SO I THOUGHT,
TILL I'M NOT
I'M JUST GOING TO
PLAY ALL MY SONGS
ON THIS DRUM.
IT SOUNDS REALLY COOL.
OH, YEAH?
LISTEN, LISTEN.
OKAY.
♪ SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ♪
♪ WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ♪
( giggles )
WOW, PHEEBS,
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I KNOW, I KNOW! AND
I'VE ONLY BEEN PLAYING
FOR, LIKE, AN HOUR.
HUH.
PHOEBE. PHOEBE, HI.
HI.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
ACTUALLY,
I CAME DOWN
TO ASK YOU
A BIG FAVOR.
OH. WELL, DON'T TELL ME
YOU WANT TO KEEP
MORE OF YOUR STUFF
IN MY UTERUS.
( laughs )
NO, NO, NO.
OH.
OKAY, NOW, SEE...
I WANT TO NAME THE
GIRL BABY "LESLIE"
AND, UM, FRANK WANTS
TO NAME ONE OF
THE BOY BABIES...
"FRANK, JR., JR."
WOULDN'T THAT BE
"FRANK THE THIRD"?
DON'T GET ME STARTED.
ANYWAY, UM, SINCE
THERE ARE THREE BABIES
AND, UM, WE BOTH GOT
TO PUT OUR NAMES IN
WE WOULD BE TRULY HONORED
IF YOU WOULD NAME
THE OTHER BOY BABY.
OH, WOW!
THAT'S SO NICE.
OH! OH! "COUGAR."
YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
YEAH.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
I LEFT A BRA DRYING
ON THE SHOWER ROD.
YOU DON'T THINK YOUR SON
WILL THINK IT'S YOURS
AND BE HORRIBLY
TRAUMATIZED?
HEY, MOMMY CAN
HAVE A WIFE
DADDY CAN HAVE A BRA.
( both chuckle )
OH, IT'S TIME TO GO.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
SEE, THAT-THAT CLOCK'S
A LITTLE FAST.
UH, WE... WE STILL
HAVE 17 MINUTES.
HUH. WHAT CAN WE DO
IN 17 MINUTES... TWICE?
WOW, THAT'S AMBITIOUS.
MMM...
( knock at door )
OKAY, YOU CAN
IGNORE THAT. IT'S...
THAT'S CAROL
WITH YOUR SON.
UH, BELIEVE ME
WHEN HE'S OLDER,
HE'LL UNDERSTAND.
Carol:
ROSS?
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
( groans )
HELLO!
HI.
HELLO.
HEY.
EMILY, THIS IS
CAROL AND SUSAN.
IT'S SO NICE
TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
YOU, TOO.
SUSAN'S SHOOTING
A COMMERCIAL
IN LONDON NEXT WEEK.
YEAH. I'M SO EXCITED.
I'VE NEVER BEEN THERE.
I'LL SHOW YOU AROUND.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
ALSO, I WAS HOPING
TO CATCH A SHOW.
SO, IF YOU CAN MAKE
ANY SUGGESTIONS...
THERE'S TONS OF
TERRIFIC STUFF.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
AH.
OH, I'M SORRY.
OH, WOW.
OH, LOOK AT YOU TWO,
BONDING
MAKING US LATE
FOR THE AIRPORT, SO...
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HE'S FINE.
IT'S JUST
US GETTING ALONG
IS DIFFICULT
FOR HIM
BECAUSE HE
DOESN'T LIKE ME.
WHAT... OH...
COME ON, THAT'S, THAT'S...
IT'S TRUE.
HI.
Joey:
HEY.
HEY, DO WE HAVE
A BABY NAME YET?
OH, NO. IT'S SO HARD.
I WENT THROUGH THIS WHOLE BOOK
AND FOUND NOTHING.
I WANT A NAME THAT'S REALLY,
LIKE, YOU KNOW
STRONG AND CONFIDENT, YOU KNOW,
LIKE-LIKE "EXXON."
WELL, IT
CERTAINLY WORKED
FOR THAT VALDEZ KID.
OH, OH! PHEEBS,
YOU WANT A STRONG NAME?
HOW ABOUT "THE HULK"?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M-I'M NOT SURE ABOUT "HULK"
BUT I LIKE THE IDEA
OF A NAME STARTING WITH "THE."
OH, YOU WANT
A GOOD NAME?
GO WITH "JOEY."
JOEY IS YOUR PAL.
JOEY IS YOUR BUDDY.
"WHERE IS EVERYBODY?"
"WELL, THEY'RE HANGING
OUT WITH JOEY."
IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO THAT
IF YOU'RE GOING
TO NAME HIM "JOEY"
YOU SHOULD NAME HIM "CHANDLER."
OH, COME ON--
CHANDLER'S FUNNY
HE'S SOPHISTICATED,
AND HE'S VERY LOVABLE
ONCE YOU GET
TO KNOW HIM.
OH, WELL, HEY
JOEY'S LOVABLE, TOO
BUT THE THING
ABOUT JOEY IS
IF YOU NEED HIM,
HE'LL BE THERE.
WELL, CHANDLER WILL BE
THERE FOR YOU, TOO.
I MEAN, HE MIGHT BE
A LITTLE LATE, BUT...
BUT HE'LL BE THERE
AND HE'LL BRING YOU
SOME COLD SODA
IF WHAT YOU NEED HIM FOR
IS THAT YOU'RE REALLY HOT.
HEY, WHAT
DO YOU SAY?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WELL, I...
I LIKE THE IDEA
OF NAMING HIM
AFTER SOMEONE I LOVE
AND "JOEY" AND "CHANDLER"
ARE BOTH GREAT NAMES...
BUT...
ALL RIGHT, I DON'T...
MAYBE I WILL JUST NAME HIM
"THE HULK."
I KNEW I SHOULDN'T
HAVE MENTIONED IT.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
TO NAME MY KID.
Rachel:
IF YOU WERE HOPING
TO SLEEP WITH JOSHUA
FOR THE FIRST TIME TONIGHT
WHICH ONE OF THESE
WOULD YOU WANT TO BE WEARING?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT REALLY CREEPS ME OUT
CHOOSING OTHER PEOPLE'S
SEX CLOTHES.
OH. I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST SO EXCITED.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS FOR
MONTHS.
GOT MY HAIR COLORED.
GOT NEW SHEETS.
MAKING HIM
A VERY FANCY MEAL.
MM-HMM...
WHAT AM I MAKING
HIM, BY THE WAY?
WELL, YOU'RE MAKING
HIM A FRISEE SALAD
WITH GOAT CHEESE
AND PINE NUTS
WILD RICE,
ROASTED ASPARAGUS
AND SALMON EN CROUTE.
I THOUGHT I WAS
MAKING HIM FILET MIGNON.
YEAH, YOU WERE, BUT THEN
YOU DECIDED TO MAKE SALMON
BECAUSE YOU HAD SOME
LEFTOVER AT THE RESTAURANT
AND THEN YOU REALIZED IF
YOU BITCHED ABOUT IT
THEN YOU WOULD
STOP COOKING
AND YOU WOULD HAVE TO MAKE
YOUR FAMOUS BAKED POTATO
AND DIET COKE.
WOW, I REALLY GET CRABBY
WHEN I COOK.
( mirthless chuckle )
HEY.
All:
SO, UH, EMILY
CALLED LAST NIGHT.
AND NOW YOU'RE
GIVING ME THE MESSAGE?
TURNS OUT THAT EMILY
IS JUST CRAZY ABOUT SUSAN. YEAH.
THEY'RE GOING
TO THE THEATER TOGETHER...
THEY'RE GOING TO DINNER...
THEY'RE GOING HORSEBACK RIDING.
GOD, SUSAN IS SO FUN.
( chuckles )
LOOK, THIS IS JUST A LITTLE
TOO FAMILIAR, OKAY?
FOR-FOR LIKE SIX MONTHS
BEFORE CAROL AND I SPLIT UP
ALL I HEARD WAS, "MY FRIEND
SUSAN IS-IS SO SMART."
"MY FRIEND SUSAN IS SO FUNNY."
"MY FRIEND SUSAN IS SO GREAT."
YOU ACTUALLY THINK
THAT SOMETHING
COULD HAPPEN
BETWEEN EMILY
AND SUSAN?
HEY, THEY'RE GOING
TO THE GYM TOGETHER.
TWO WOMEN?
STRETCHING?
YOU KNOW, THEY TAKE
A STEAM TOGETHER,
THINGS GET A LITTLE PLAYFUL...
DIDN'T YOU SEE PERSONAL BEST?
NO, BUT I'M GONNA.
HI! HI! YOU'RE CRAZY.
THIS IS EMILY.
EMILY IS STRAIGHT.
YEAH, HOW
DO YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE THOUGHT
CAROL WAS STRAIGHT
BEFORE I
MARRIED HER.
YEAH, I'M DEFINITELY...
I DON'T LIKE
THE NAME "ROSS."
WHAT A WEIRD WAY TO
KICK ME WHEN I'M DOWN.
NO, NO. NO, I JUST...
I MEANT FOR THE BABY.
OH.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH "ROSS"?
WELL, IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
WOULD NEVER HAPPEN
TO, LIKE,
THE HULK, YOU KNOW.
ACTUALLY, THAT-
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
IN THE INCREDIBLE
HULK, UH, NUMBER 72
DR. BRUCE BANNER
FOUND-FOUND...
YOU KNOW... NEVER MIND.
MY GIRLFRIEND'S
A LESBIAN.
SO, I DECIDED
I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO GO
WITH EITHER "JOEY"
OR "CHANDLER."
OH!
OH, OH, OH, OH!
YOU GOT TO PICK "JOEY."
I MEAN, NAME ONE FAMOUS
PERSON NAMED "CHANDLER."
RAYMOND CHANDLER.
SOMEONE YOU DIDN'T MAKE UP.
( scoffs )
OKAY, THERE ARE NO
FAMOUS "JOEYS," EXCEPT FOR...
( chuckles )
JOEY BUTTAFUOCO.
YEAH, THAT GUY REALLY HURT US.
YEAH.
WELL, HOW ABOUT A COMPROMISE,
THEN, OKAY?
WHAT IF IT'S, YOU KNOW...
"CHANOEY"?
OKAY, LOOK--
"JOEY"?
COME ON, THINK ABOUT IT.
FIRST OF ALL,
HE'LL NEVER BE PRESIDENT.
I MEAN, THERE'S NEVER GOING
TO BE A PRESIDENT JOEY.
ALL RIGHT, MAN,
I DIDN'T WANT TO BRING THIS UP
BUT "CHANDLER"
IS THE STUPIDEST NAME
I EVER HEARD IN MY LIFE.
IT'S NOT EVEN A NAME.
IT'S BARELY EVEN A WORD, OKAY?
IT'S KIND OF LIKE "CHANDELIER"
BUT IT'S NOT.
ALL RIGHT?
IT'S A STUPID, STUPID NON-NAME.
WOW, YOU... YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE
A HORRIBLE, HORRIBLE NAME.
( sighs )
I'M SORRY, MAN.
I DIDN'T...
I'M-I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
OKAY.
SO, I GUESS IT'S
"JOEY," THEN.
THIS IS SO NICE.
THANK YOU
FOR DOING THIS.
OH, PLEASE. COOKING SOOTHES ME.
( both chuckle )
( sighs )
SO, DIG IN.
RIGHT. OH, IT ALL
LOOKS SO GOOD.
MMM.
MMM!
OH, MY GOD.
OH, I KNOW.
MY GOD, THIS IS SO...
THIS RICE IS SO...
I'M SO GOOD.
BEHIND YOU.
OH, YEAH, SORRY.
THEY USED TO LIVE HERE
AND SOMETIMES
THEY MIGRATE BACK OVER.
IS THERE, UH...
IS THERE SOME WAY
THAT THEY COULD, UH...
NOT BE HERE?
IT'S JUST THAT, UH, FARM BIRDS
REALLY KIND OF FREAK ME OUT.
YEAH, SURE, OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY, GREAT.
COME ON.
SHOO. SHOO.
HERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO. WHOA!
SHOO. SHOO.
ALL RIGHT. WHOA!
OH, SORRY.
COME HERE.
GOOD. THERE YOU GO.
OKAY.
( Joshua clears throat )
HEY, HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
COME ON.
COME HERE.
ALL GONE.
( weak chuckle )
SO, FARM BIRDS, HUH?
YEAH. IT'S, UH, IT'S
MY ONLY WEIRD THING, I SWEAR.
AND I-I-I WOULD'VE TOLD YOU
ABOUT IT
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT THEY WOULD... BE HERE.
( chuckles ):
OH, OKAY.
SO, ALL RIGHT...
( clears throat )
( chuckles )
OKAY.
( nervous groan )
SO, CAN I SERVE YOU
A LITTLE OF...
WHAT? WHAT'S...? WHAT?
NOTHING. I, UH...
IT'S JUST THAT I KNOW THAT
THEY'RE STILL OUT THERE.
BUT THEY'RE ACROSS THE HALL.
I MEAN, THAT'S TWO DOORS AWAY.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE THEM
A LONG TIME
TO PECK THEIR WAY
BACK OVER HERE.
( nervous chuckle )
HEY, THAT'S-THAT'S
NOT FUNNY.
UH...
OKAY, YOU KNOW...
WOULD YOU FEEL BETTER
IF WE WENT
SOMEPLACE ELSE?
I MEAN, WE COULD PACK
ALL THIS STUFF UP
AND, YOU KNOW,
GO TO YOUR APARTMENT.
OH, THEY'RE WORKING
ON IT THIS WEEK.
IT'S A TOTAL MESS.
BUT I'M STAYING AT
MY PARENTS' HOUSE.
WE COULD GO THERE.
YOUR PARENTS?
THEY'RE OUT OF TOWN.
OH.
YEAH, IT'S A HUGE PLACE,
AND-AND IT'S GOT
THIS GORGEOUS VIEW
OF THE PARK.
IT'D BE VERY,
VERY ROMANTIC.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YEAH, THAT WORKS.
( clucking )
YEAH, THEY-THEY CAN
SMELL THE FEAR.
OKAY, IT'S OKAY.
( clears throat )
HEY.
HI.
HOW'S BEN?
WELL, I ASKED HIM
IF HE WANTED TO EAT
HE SAID, "NO."
I ASKED HIM
IF HE WANTED TO SLEEP
HE SAID, "NO."
I ASKED HIM
WHAT HE WANTED TO DO
HE SAID, "NO,"
SO HE'S SWEEPING.
HEY, BUDDY.
HEY.
SO, UM...
ANY WORD FROM SUSAN?
OH, YEAH. SHE SAID
SHE'S HAVING SO MUCH FUN
WITH EMILY.
UH-HUH, UH-HUH.
UH, BY THE BY, DID IT, UH...
DID IT EVER OCCUR TO YOU
THAT, I DON'T KNOW
MAYBE THEY MIGHT BE HAVING
A LITTLE TOO MUCH FUN?
WHAT'S "TOO MUCH FUN"?
YOU KNOW, THE KIND OF FUN
YOU AND SUSAN HAD
WHEN WE WERE MARRIED.
( chuckles )
OH, MY GOD, YOU ARE SO PARANOID.
AM I?
YES.
LOOK, I CAN'T
SPEAK FOR EMILY
BUT SUSAN IS IN A LOVING,
COMMITTED RELATIONSHIP.
UH-HUH, CAROL,
SO WERE WE.
ALL RIGHT, JUST IMAGINE
FOR A MOMENT
THAT SUSAN MEETS SOMEONE,
AND THEY REALLY HIT IT OFF.
SAY THEY'RE COMING BACK
FROM THE THEATER
AND THEY STOP AT A PUB
FOR A COUPLE OF DRINKS.
THEY'RE LAUGHING,
YOU KNOW.
SOMEONE INNOCENTLY
TOUCHES SOMEONE ELSE.
THERE'S ELECTRICITY.
IT'S NEW, IT'S EXCITING.
ARE YOU TELLING ME
THERE ISN'T EVEN
THE SLIGHTEST POSSIBILITY
OF SOMETHING HAPPENING?
MAYBE...
OH MY GOD!
I DIDN'T REALLY BELIEVE IT
UNTIL YOU SAID IT!
...AND EVEN THOUGH
NONE OF THE KIDS BELIEVED ME
I SWEAR TO GOD,
THAT DUCK PUSHED ME.
YEAH.
WOW, THIS PLACE
IS FABULOUS!
LET ME SHOW YOU AROUND.
THIS IS THE DOWNSTAIRS
LIVING ROOM...
WHAT? THERE'S TWO LIVING ROOMS?
GOD, GROWING UP HERE
THIS PLACE MUST
HAVE BEEN A REAL BABE MAGNET.
YEAH, WELL,
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
BUT MY PARENTS
JUST MOVED HERE.
OH, WELL, YOU
SHOULD KNOW
THIS PLACE IS
A REAL BABE MAGNET.
WANT TO MAKE OUT?
YEAH. OKAY.
MMM.
HERE'S AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T I PUT THE FOOD
IN THE FRIDGE
AND WE CAN EAT IT LATER?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
UM, IS THERE A PLACE THAT
I COULD GO FRESHEN UP?
YEAH, YEAH.
UM, JUST DOWN THE HALL
AND, UH, SECOND DOOR
TO YOUR LEFT.
OH, HI, DARLING.
MOM, DAD! WHAT ARE
YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
WE CUT THE TRIP SHORT.
FRANCE SUCKS!
UM, THIS MAY BE A LITTLE WEIRD
BUT I... I'VE GOT A DATE HERE.
WELL, SAY NO MORE.
WE'LL GRAB SOME FOOD
AND TAKE IT UPSTAIRS
AND BE OUT OF YOUR HAIR.
OH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
SO, YOU DIDN'T GET TO ITALY?
YEP. SUCKS!
HI, YOU.
OH, MY GOD...
I KNOW.
I CAN DO MORE THAN COOK.
UH...
I LIKE HER.
SHE SEEMS SMART.
UH... RACHEL,
MY PARENTS.
OH, SO NICE
TO MEET YOU.
HI, RACHEL.
HELLO. HELLO.
OH, JOSHUA...
THAT $500 WAS
FOR GROCERIES.
WHAT? TH-TH-THIS? NO.
OH, NO, THIS IS NOT...
THAT'S NOT WHAT...
THAT'S NOT WHAT IT IS.
YOU SEE, OKAY,
I WORK IN FASHION.
SEE, AND-AND THIS IS
A REAL DRESS, ACTUALLY.
IT IS...
THEY'RE-THEY'RE
WEARING IT IN MILAN.
IT'S TH... AND...
SEE, OH, PART OF MY JOB
IS TO WEAR THE CLOTHES
AND THEN I SEE
HOW PEOPLE RESPOND
AND THEN I REPORT BACK
TO MY SUPERIORS
AT BLOOMINGDALE'S.
SO...
AND, OBVIOUSLY, IN, UH,
IN-IN THIS CASE
I AM-AM GOING TO REPORT BACK
"U.S.A. NOT READY."
MAYBE IN L.A.
YES.
THERE YOU GO.
SO, HAVE YOU KIDS
EATEN YET?
WELL, WE WERE GOING
TO DO THAT AFTER.
I MEAN, UM...
NEXT.
WELL, WE'RE STARVING.
WHY DON'T WE
GET SOMETHING TO EAT?
OH... YEAH.
WELL...
YEAH, NO USE WASTING THIS BABY
JUST LYING AROUND THE HOUSE.
SO... WE'LL GO EAT.
Rachel:
YEAH.
YOU'LL WEAR THAT.
WE'LL BE EATING, AND, OF COURSE,
YOU'LL BE... WEARING THAT.
DUDE, I AM SORRY
ABOUT WHAT I SAID.
NOPE, NOPE,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS A RIDICULOUS NAME.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
YES, IT IS.
FROM NOW ON, I HAVE
NO FIRST NAME.
SO...
YOU'RE JUST BING?
I HAVE NO NAME.
ALL RIGHT, SO, WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO CALL YOU?
OKAY, UH, FOR
NOW, TEMPORARILY
YOU CAN CALL ME....
CLINT.
( snickers )
NO WAY ARE YOU COOL ENOUGH
TO PULL OFF CLINT.
OKAY, SO, WHAT NAME AM I
COOL ENOUGH TO PULL OFF?
UM... GENE.
IT'S CLINT.
IT'S CLINT!
SEE YOU LATER, GENE.
BYE, GENE.
IT'S CLINT!
CLINT!
WHAT'S UP WITH GENE?
Monica:
YOU WORE YOUR NIGHTIE
TO DINNER?
OH, YEAH.
AND, UH, THE
BEST PART, THOUGH
WAS WHEN THE, UH, WAITER
SPILLED WATER DOWN MY BACK.
I JUMPED UP AND
MY BOOB POPPED OUT.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, NO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT--
I GOT NICE BOOBS.
SO, I JUST PICKED UP
A MESSAGE FROM EMILY.
SHE AND SUSAN ARE GOING
TO A POETRY READING TOGETHER.
SO?
POETRY?
SUSAN'S GAY.
THEY'RE BEING GAY TOGETHER!
BUT EMILY'S STRAIGHT.
OH, WAKE UP!
WOW...
CAROL REALLY
MESSED YOU UP.
EXCUSE ME?
YEAH, SHE TURNED YOU
INTO THIS-THIS-THIS
UNTRUSTING, CRAZY,
JEALOUS SYCOPHANT.
ALL RIGHT, SO I DON'T KNOW
WHAT SYCOPHANT MEANS
BUT THE REST IS RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I AM NOT A CRAZY,
JEALOUS PERSON.
HUH.
WHAT?
SHE'S TOTALLY RIGHT.
WHEN WE WERE TOGETHER,
YOU GOT FREAKED OUT ABOUT MARK
AND NOTHING WAS GOING ON.
THIS TOTALLY
MAKES SENSE.
IT DOES NOT.
SURE IT DOES.
IN HIGH SCHOOL
YOU WEREN'T
JEALOUS AT ALL
EVEN THOUGH ALL
YOUR GIRLFRIENDS
WERE CHEATING
ON YOU.
( Phoebe gasps )
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT
SO, UP UNTIL '92, '93,
HE WAS VERY TRUSTING.
THEN '94 HIT,
CAROL LEFT HIM
AND BAM, PARANOID CITY.
Rachel:
YEP. ABSOLUTELY.
ABSOLUTELY.
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
THIS IS NOT FUN!
ALL RIGHT, LOOK...
ALL WE'RE TRYING
TO SAY IS
DON'T LET WHAT
HAPPENED WITH CAROL
RUIN WHAT YOU'VE
GOT WITH EMILY.
THE '92 ROSS WOULDN'T.
THANKS.
STILL THINK I WAS RIGHT
ABOUT THAT WHOLE MARK THING
THOUGH.
WHA... YA... WHA...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HOPE EMILY IS A LESBIAN.
( drum rattling )
DRUM ROLL.
OKAY, OKAY...
ALL RIGHT.
HELP.
AM I A MARK OR A JOHN?
WELL, YOU'RE NOT TALL
ENOUGH TO BE A MARK...
BUT YOU MIGHT MAKE
A GOOD BARNEY.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
I'M SERIOUS, OKAY?
TOMORROW AT 3:30
I'M GOING DOWN
TO THE COURTHOUSE.
YOU'LL ACTUALLY GO
THROUGH WITH THIS?
HEY, LOOK, THIS NAME HAS BEEN
HOLDING ME BACK MY ENTIRE LIFE.
OKAY, IT'S PROBABLY WHY KIDS
PICKED ON ME IN SCHOOL
AND WHY I NEVER DO WELL
WITH WOMEN.
SO, AS OF 4:00 TOMORROW,
I'M EITHER GOING TO BE
MARK JOHNSON
OR JOHN MARKSON.
YOU'VE GOT PROBLEMS
BECAUSE OF YOU,
NOT YOUR NAME.
ALL RIGHT, THIS
HAS GOT TO STOP.
CHANDLER IS
A GREAT NAME.
IN FACT...
YES.
I'M... I'M SORRY.
I KNOW YOU
REALLY WANTED ME
TO NAME THE BABY
JOEY, BUT...
SO, I'M-I'M GOING TO...
I'M GOING TO NAME
THE BABY CHANDLER.
REALLY?
YEAH, BUT YOU HAVE
TO KEEP THE NAME, TOO.
OKAY.
THANKS.
YOU WANT TO HUG IT OUT?
YEAH.
YAY.
YAY. OH, YAY!
OKAY, I GOT TO GO TELL
FRANK AND ALICE RIGHT NOW.
OOH.
GOOD-BYE, PHEEBS.
OKAY, BYE.
( devious laughter )
( horrified gasp )
( both moaning )
THAT'S NICE LUGGAGE.
YEAH, I WAS
GOING TO SAY.
HEY!
HI!
I MISSED YOU.
OH, I MISSED
YOU, TOO.
HEY, THANKS
FOR EVERYTHING.
I HAD SUCH A GREAT TIME.
OH, SO DID I.
THERE'S NO TONGUE.
( sighs )